https://www.cmacable.com/privacy-policy/

ProductsPerformax™ Control CablesPush-Pull CablesPull Pull CablesSafety & RestraintPlastiCableCycle-Flex Miniature CablesRemote Actuation CablesElectricalWiring HarnessesLeads Engineering ResourcesCable CreatorOnline CatalogOnline BrochureDownloadable CADDesign ConsiderationsDesign GuidesWhitepapersCase StudiesTerms & DefinitionsQualityDocumentationAffiliationsCase StudiesQuality Awards Customer ServiceCustomer SupportTerms & ConditionsCMA is recognized by our customers as providing superior customer service in terms of responsiveness and on time delivery.Contact Headquarters 10896 Industrial Parkway NW PO Box 409 Bolivar, Ohio Email: Toll-free: 800-586-8404 Phone: 330-874-2900Cable CreatorPrivacy PolicyWhat information do we collect? We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)To respond to inquiriesThe email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.Do we use cookies? We do not use cookies.Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.This policy was last modified on 11/1/12Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.cmacable.com PO Box 409 Bolivar, Ohio 44612-0409 United States of America
(330)874-2900This policy is powered by Trust Guard PCI compliance.Request A QuoteCMA’s Design Engineers are glad to work directly with you to develop a quote for your specific application.Create a PrototypeUse our Cable Creator to easily build a prototype of the cable assembly you need and submit it to our engineering team. Create a Prototype.Download Design GuidesOur design engineering team has put together an in depth look at designing cables for various applications.Download WhitepapersOur whitepapers address concrete topics like whether or not to apply tinning, how to account for lost motion, and more.CartNo products in the cart.
